VibeGuard
Guard your vibe. Catch what AI missed.
$ vibeguard scan demo --package-verification seed --fail-on none
VibeGuard scanned 1 file(s).
3 active finding(s), 0 dismissed.
[CRITICAL] hallucinated_package_npm (L1)
"react-virtualized-auto-sizer" does not exist in npm.
This may be a slopsquatting risk.
Verified alternatives: react-virtualized, react-window
[CRITICAL] hardcoded_secret_openai_key (L1)
OpenAI API key appears to be hardcoded.
Move the secret to an environment variable or OS keychain.
Rotate the exposed value.
[HIGH] sast_xss_inner_html (L2)
HTML is assigned directly to the DOM.
Use textContent for plain text or sanitize trusted HTML.
VS Code | JetBrains | CI
vibeguard.dev